1.  Read the MySQL 5.7 Reference Manual 6.4.3 The General Query Log , https://dev.mysql.com/doc/refman/5.7/en/query-log.html

Enable the general query log for your local MySQL instance. 

2.   Practice the following sections according to http://www.mysqltutorial.org/
All the SQL statements should be excuted on your local DB  (The instance installed on your laptop).

MySQL Administration，	http://www.mysqltutorial.org/mysql-administration.aspx

server address: 172.31.34.145    [ port：3306 ]
username：your SN
pass：your SN

GUI is not allowed to connect to the MySQL Server.
only command line interface for this assignment. All the SQL statements should be completed. Statement execution process itself is part of your performance. 
Upload your general log to the incoming directory of ftp server ftp://dbms:dbms@202.205.101.168 
Name your general query log as $SN.log. Please replace $SN with your student number.

You are not a copy machine. Please READ through the tutorial.

3.	Create a account on github.com, finish the "hello world" sample. 
	Create a text file named as $SN.git , input the URL of your "hello world" project and upload the $SN.git file to the incoming directory of ftp server.


due: 2017-04-05 8:00AM          



